A sound soul dwells within a sound mind and a sound body.
Fine. He's all yours. Be careful. No stupid moves.
Yeah.
Give me a shout if you get yourself into trouble.
I'll bail you out if you're sorry, but need saving.
Yeah, okay. I get it. Thanks for the support. Now go already.
Maka, let's go.
Tsubaki, we're heading after a kid and the others.
Great. I won't let you pass me.
Speed star.
See ya. Have fun.
That's okay. I can handle this.
People are easier to deal with when their backs are turned.
Die, okay?
No way!
Hey, that's no fair.
Nice punch. Cutting him won't do any good because of the black blood.
Some more impact strikes like that are what we need.
We have to stop him here. We'll do a side catch, then a left rush.
This body's so hard, it feels like I'm punching lead.
Krona, quit thinking about the brat who ran off and focus on the one who's right in front of you.
Round one goes to me.
I don't understand.
Why am I suddenly all beat up?
I don't know what to do.
How am I supposed to deal with a girl who keeps punching me like that?
Kill her.
I think we can safely say your first attack went well enough.
But let's face it, you picked a fight with a demon sword.
Do you have any chance of winning?
Tell me you do.
Tell me you have a shot.
Nope, not really.
How are you so smart yet so stupid at the same time, Maka?
This is awesome.
It's official.
You're definitely the coolest partner ever.
Well, you'll manage somehow.
Yeah, I'll figure something out.
Don't be an idiot, girl.
You're not gonna manage anything.
Don't you remember how this went last time?
You and your weapon didn't manage so well.
I don't know why I even bother with you anyway.
A puny little soul like yours is hardly even worth eating.
That star brat from earlier looked a lot tastier than you.
You're an unappetizing, useless little girl.
I don't even need to fight you.
I can probably bully you to death from here.
Hooray.
You finally see me for who I am.
The last time we fought, you only saw me as food, not as an opponent.
But this time is different.
This time you're seeing me as a person.
So I say, hooray.
And as for that meister of yours, why are you always so nervous?
It's pathetic.
Leave me alone.
Why don't you understand?
You're such a weakling.
You'll just lose again.
Why do you insist on fighting when you know you can't beat me?
Don't look at me like that.
That's a determined stare you're giving me and I don't know how to deal with it.
It's very unsettling.
It may be true that I'm physically weaker than you, but somehow I don't think I'm going to lose.
You see, my soul is stronger than yours is.
Blabber all you want.
No one will hear your screams when you lose.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Have I made you a bit angry?
My name's Maka.
I'm a scythemeister.
Tell me who you are.
Demon swordsman Krona.
I challenge you, Krona.
That's good.
You look less scared now.
Maka.
So now I know the name of the person I'm supposed to kill.
I challenge you, Krona.
六人目も合わさず運命まで絡んでく。
行き先もらったポテル 食えない夜を恥で
不可愛しすぎた眩しさが 悪い夢に続いても
繋いだ魂の火が胸を刺すなら 言葉よりもっと強い響きが今聞こえるか
出会った訳は途絶び 引き付けられて
触れた瞬間も 傷の分だけ確かになれる
我の人は未成長がつくる
はい 見えない
見えない
カナシアガキ奴トレイズの悪魔力?
マーカでくる気に飽みます
またここで
マーカで準備よ
his heart and blood turned back into liquid bloody needle
this guy means business ragnarok shut up scream resonance
tell me why are you collecting innocent souls and reviving the keys in chrono
because i'm always scared if i can get stronger and more powerful i'll be able to deal with things
better and lady medusa will abandon me if i don't become a kishin if i don't get stronger i'll always
be afraid reach out bring it on i may be weaker than you but i'll take on whatever you throw at me
may i ask you something
where did you abduct the child who became the demon sword meister your first plan was to use
the demon sword to create a kishin wasn't it but now you're more interested in reviving the kishin
sleeping under the academy that's because your first idea isn't working out right the demon sword
is failing you it shows no sign of becoming a kishin anytime soon so instead you risk using the
black blood to wake asherah and now you're left with a child you have no use for it looks like
your grand experiment has failed and pretty soon everyone's going to know it
why the laughter did i say something that amuses you medusa you really are a fool aren't you
it may look like i failed to you professor stein but all of my work has pertained to the black blood
from the very beginning oh and one other thing another part of your theory that is completely wrong
i didn't abduct the demon sword meister from anywhere you see krona is my own child oh dear
you shouldn't have gotten back up
why are you still so insistent on fighting me you're never going to win just give up i'm tired of
trying to figure out how to deal with you
he used his blood again cutting attacks like that are the wrong way to go the more he bleeds the worse
off we're gonna be yeah i know but there is one more thing we can try you're right there is that
let's go maca
come on get it in gear krona
scream resonance
we need to increase our resonance rate
such strong resonance energy so it's beginning
so it's beginning
scream
witch hunter
screech gamma
hey stein what's going on out there
the black blood is being activated
oh really is that all you've got
he took those hits without even blinking
how can a two-spick like him be so strong
it isn't him soul his body itself may be weak
but the black blood flowing through his veins strengthens
ragnarok hardens krona's body so it withstands our blows
all right now it's my turn
rage gamma
stop it stop it no
no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no stop it don't make me cut your weapon now
just forget about that other crumb okay you need to f cuộcãy into your car
okay right now
come on soul there's no point in struggling
struggling anymore and you know it it's time to wake up and accept the inevitable let me make you
stronger are you hanging in there soul yeah there's something i think i almost have it
i sensed something earlier like there was no way i could lose it's something in crona's
wavelength that i can almost grasp if i just had more time
no are you afraid now
you remind me of the little one i still don't know how to deal with it either
you have that much in common at least
now defeat it crona
i can't do it i don't know how to deal with something like this now
you are a bad child i want you out of my sight this is your punishment you'll be locked in this room
for a long long time so get used to it no please pick another punishment it's too dark in here i can't see
anything you can't leave the two of us alone please don't
it's so dark in here i don't know how to deal with darkness like this
damn it crona look what you did no ragnarok you gotta be locked up in here with you because you
couldn't pull yourself together it hurts quit it you're always clicking on me and it's not nice
stop twisting my nose like that it hurts i can't see anything in here
but i know i have a nose plate now it's all your fault you idiot
take this take this take this take this take this take this i'm gonna punch you until i can't punch
anymore crona
you can come out now
come we're picking up where we left off you will defeat it this time crona
there's no way i can't do it i still don't know how to deal with something like that
you can stay in there out of my sight a little longer
damn it crona you complete idiot
ow stop it you're hurting me again
leave me alone how many times have we done this now and how many more times are we going to have
to do it this is getting you nowhere crona
did you know my blood is black
yeah
or
right
um
Bye-bye, you little one.
Come on, Sol. Now is the time to act.
Maka.
You're going to die if you don't do something.
Why not just leave it to me?
Do away with reason.
Let me make you stronger.
Not happening.
You can give me power.
That's all.
My reason stays with me.
Oh, no.
You can't beat the Demon Sword's madness that way.
You're sadly mistaken if you think reason and discipline will give you the power you need now.
Those aren't enough. I've never seen anyone have it that easy.
Understanding fear, then fighting against it.
Maintaining complete discipline always.
Those are great powers in their own right.
Besides, this isn't just about me anymore.
If we resonate any higher, Maka will be affected, too.
Don't be an idiot, you damn brat. You're turning into a pathetic whiner all of a sudden.
What happened to all that spirit you used to have?
Where's your drive? Forget reasons.
Just let loose and go crazy for once.
What kind of life can you live without a little bit of insanity thrown in?
Shut up! Why are you even talking? You're just saying the same damn thing over and over again.
I'm so sick of listening to you. I could puke. You're full of crap and I don't listen to crap.
You got it?
So just shut your stupid little demon mouth and take the lead. I'll decide if I want to follow you or not. How about that?
How can I shut my mouth and take the lead?
I don't know. Just point or something, you stupid freak.
Okay, okay. Let's just cool down for a second here.
You and I both want to move forward.
But it isn't going to work this way. We can't make progress if we keep on yelling at each other like this.
Right?
Yeah.
Now, I invited somebody over to join us.
You can come in now.
Huh? Who's there?
Now that we're all here, perhaps we can decide things in a more agreeable manner. What do you say?
Maka?
I heard most of what's going on.
How did you get here?
What is this? Some kind of weird meeting inside my brain or something?
It's simple, really. Your souls are resonating right now.
Is it so difficult to believe that your minds could be connected as well?
All right, demon. How do I know this isn't just some image of Maka you created? Why should I trust you?
You're a very cautious young man, aren't you?
Remember, it's your mind we're inside of now. You're running the show.
There's only so much I can do in here.
Maka!
Yeah, okay. It's Maka.
Now then, why don't we put on some nice, relaxing music?
You're going to have to lead. I'm not sure how to do this.
It's fine. Let's do whatever.
Five and six and seven and eight.
I don't understand, Maka. What are you doing here?
Did you hear the demon guy's voice, too?
I'm not sure. Maybe.
Thinking about it, it is possible I heard it faintly before, back when we fought the immortal werewolf.
Yes. That would certainly make sense. I had entered U2 at that point.
But I was removed shortly after I got there. I'm still not sure how, though.
If that's really what happened, then you shouldn't be here. You managed to get rid of the demon.
You might not be so lucky the next time, you know?
Hey, when our wavelengths are matched like this, you can tell what I'm thinking. Can't you, Sol?
Are you?
You can't seriously be thinking of using the black blood to give yourself the same madness Krona has.
I knew you'd be angry.
It's something I sensed when I used Witch Hunter on him earlier.
Something I could almost grasp, but not quite.
If I could be as powerful as him,
Maybe I would know.
Maybe I could figure out what I needed to about Krona.
No way.
It's too dangerous to do that without knowing more.
If you do this, you could end up as crazy as Krona forever.
Yeah.
I'm sorry, Sol.
I've made up my mind.
We can't be sure you'll return to normal.
I know, but it's worth trying, right?
All right, fine.
I give.
Do whatever crazy things you want to.
Just remember, no matter how far away you end up,
I'm still your weapon, and I will pull you back.
Ow!
Oh, sorry.
You really should lead, okay?
Uh-huh.
I see that now.
This is more like it.
Oh, he flew!
I'm being pulled into the madness with her!
Maka, I swear I will not let go of you!
You're wrong about that one, fool.
See, I'm the one who's leading now.
Maka, I swear I will not let go of you!
Thank you.
You could have told me sooner.
On the next episode of Soul Eater, may my soul reach you.
A dry heart inside unbearable isolation.
Watch it, or I'll take your soul, mister.